<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>WELCOME</title>
        <subtitle></subtitle>
        <icon>https://xjp66666.github.io/assets/favicon.ico</icon>
        <link>https://xjp66666.github.io</link>
        <author>
          <name>YUZU ATRI</name>
        </author>
        <description>math hater &amp; vn enjoyer</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">https://xjp66666.github.io/2026/02/20/hello-world/</guid>
            <title>Hello World</title>
            <link>https://xjp66666.github.io/2026/02/20/hello-world/</link>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;h3 id=&#34;why-hexo&#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#why-hexo&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt; Why Hexo&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few years ago, when I was in elementary school, I build my first web blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason was because one day when my math teacher was chanting lullaby as usual and I was whispering to my desk mate in order to not fall asleep. I can&#39;t remember why I said that but &amp;quot;I wish I could have my own website. That would be sooo cool&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coincidentally he is a computer tech master. Yes. When everyone was forced to study 15 hours a day, he still managed to take some time to learn Coding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Why not using Hexo?&amp;quot; he said, &amp;quot;its neat, easy-to-use, and highly customizable. You don&#39;t even have to write a single line of html code cuz Hexo is capable of generating static web pages from your markdown files.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;first-try&#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#first-try&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt; First try&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back then I had no idea what he was talking about and what he meant by &amp;quot;run hexo on github ci and deploy your website on github pages&amp;quot;. So I search for tutorials after getting home and spent the whole night and finally figured out that html and markdown are not programming languages. They are actually mark up languages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started building it in the summer vacation that came after my grade 7 school year. It took me almost two weeks. Days and nights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At that time(2022) people still thought that &amp;quot;AI&amp;quot; is some kind of advanced tech and it would only exist in sci-fis, although ChatGPT went viral not long after the beginning of 2023. So when I ran into problems, the best I could do was googling. I assume when you&#39;re reading this article, most people have already given up using search engines, but that&#39;s for later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And when I finally finished my masterpiece, I couldn&#39;t describe how thrilled I was cuz it was the first time I literally built something I was proud of, all on my own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I posted it online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I showed it off to my classmates, my parents, my teachers, although it seemed nobody really cared.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also bought a .site domain for it()&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was already tired of those compliments from others, so nothing could let me down even if no one else saw my work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, maybe except for my schoolwork.&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
